fifacoin.com 2017-12-08

# Privacy Policy

##  Privacy Policy 

**FifaCoin.com Privacy Policy**

**1\. What Do We Do with Your Information?**  
We'll collect the personal information you gave us including name and email address when you sell and buy FIFA Ultimate Team coins here. Our system will also automatically receive your IP address when you browse any page of FifaCoin.com. If applicable, we may email you newsletters about our giveaways, events or anything you may interest, with your permission.

**2\. How Do You Get Our Consent?**  
When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only. If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like subscribe to newsletters, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

**3\. How Do You Withdraw Your Consent?**  
If you change your mind after opt-in, you can withdraw your consent for us to contact you and for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information at anytime by contacting us at support#fifacoin.com（Replace "#" to "@"）

**4\. Disclosure**  
We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

**5\. Third-party Services**  
Generally, the third-party providers cooperated with us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us. However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions. For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers. In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.  
For example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act. Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

**6\. Security**  
To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed. If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

**7\. Cookies**  
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.  
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**8\. Age Of Consent**  
By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site. 

**9\. Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it. If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

**10\. Questions and Contact Information**  
If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact us at support#fifacoin.com（Replace "#" to "@"）
